<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SoloRestorant</string>
    <string name="term">Article 1 (Purpose)

These terms and conditions shall be governed by O O Company (e-commerce operator).

Related to the Internet provided by the OO Cyber Mall (hereinafter referred to as the "

In using the service (as referred to as the "service"), the cyber mall and

The purpose of this Chapter is to prescribe the rights obligations and responsibilities of users.



Article 2 (Definitions)

1 The term "mall" means goods or services (hereinafter referred to as "goods, etc.") by OO company.

Using information and communication facilities, such as computers, to provide to users

This refers to a virtual place of business where goods, etc. can be traded.

It is also used in the meaning of operators who operate cyber malls.


2 The term "user" means access to the "mall" in accordance with these terms and conditions.

services provided by the Mall"

Refers to the members and non-members who receive the .


3 The term "member" is a person who has registered as a member of the "mall", and continues to be a "mall".

Refers to those who can use the services they provide.


4 The term "non-members" means that they do not sign up as members, but are provided by the "mall".

This refers to the person who uses the service.



Article 3 (statement, explanation, and revision of terms and conditions, etc.

1 "Mall" shall be the contents of this Agreement and the name of the trade name and representative;

place of business address

(including addresses where consumer complaints can be addressed);

telephone number facsimile transmission number e-mail address, business registration number, mail-order business

To make it easier for users to know the report number, person in charge of personal information management, etc.

Post on the initial service screen (front) of the 00 Cyber Mall.

However, the contents of the terms and conditions can be viewed through a connected screen.

I can do it.

2 "Mall shall be set in the terms and conditions before the user agrees to the terms and conditions.

Important information, such as the conditions for refund of responsibility for delivery of Cheong Wa Dae Yakchulhoi, etc.

For users to understand the contents, a separate connection screen or

The ruling and opposition parties should seek the user's confirmation by providing a pop-up screen, etc.

3 The "mall" shall be the Act on the Protection of Consumers in Electronic Commerce, etc.,

the Act on the Regulation of Terms and Conditions, the Framework Act on Electronic Documents and Electronic Trade, 「

Electronic Financial Transactions Act, Electronic Signature Act, 「

The Act on the Promotion of Information and Communications Network Utilization and Information Protection, etc., 「

the Act on door-to-door sales, etc., the Framework Act on Consumers, etc.

You may amend this Agreement to the extent that it does not violate the relevant laws.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

</resources>